Redwood JS an opinionated full stack JavaScript framework for building big
Redwood JS 是一个自以为是的全栈JavaScript 框架，用于构建
ambitious startups as we all know the JavaScript ecosystem is incredibly
雄心勃勃的大型初创公司，因为我们都知道JavaScript 生态系统非常
complex with millions of different tools to choose from when architecting an app
复杂，在构建应用程序时有数百万种不同的工具可供选择
Redwood takes a collection of the most battle tested Technologies like react
Redwood 收集了经过大量实战考验的技术，例如 react
Prisma graphql storybook and jest then weaves them together so developers can
Prisma graphql 故事书 然后 jest将它们编织在一起，以便开发人员可以
get things done quickly and reliably it was developed by a team of software
快速可靠地完成工作 它是由一个软件工程师团队开发的
Engineers that includes the co-founder of GitHub and hit version 1.0 in 2022 it
，其中包括 GitHub 的联合创始人，并在 2022 年推出 1.0 版它
has its own custom router for server-side rendering but unlike many
有自己的用于服务器端渲染的自定义路由器，但是 与许多
other Frameworks it doesn't use the file system and instead puts all routes in a
其他框架不同，它不使用文件系统，而是将所有路由放在
single file with automatic code splitting for each page most importantly
一个文件中，并为每个页面自动进行代码拆分，最重要的是，
though it provides abstractions to connect your front-end UI to a back-end
尽管它提供了抽象来
relational database via a graphql API its rails inspired CLI can quickly
通过 a 将前端 UI 连接到后端关系数据库 graphql API其 rails 启发的 CLI 可以快速
generate the code required to build complex features and not just build them
生成构建复杂功能所需的代码，而不仅仅是 构建它们，
but also test them with jest and storybook it ships with Apollo client by
但也使用 jest 和storybook 测试它们默认情况下它与 Apollo 客户端一起提供，
default making it easy for the front end to consume data from the graphql API and
使前端可以轻松地使用来自 graphql API 的数据，并且
when it comes time for deployment the code can easily run on a standalone
当需要部署时，代码可以轻松地在独立
server or your favorite serverless infrastructure to get started generate a
服务器或您最喜欢的服务器上运行开始使用无服务器基础设施
new Redwood project with yarn the front end code is managed in the web directory
使用 yarn 生成一个新的 Redwood 项目前端代码在 web 目录中管理
it's a react app that's wrapped with the Redwood provider with routes as the main
它是一个反应应用程序，与Redwood 提供程序一起包装，路由
entry point for the UI the routes component is a collection of URL
作为 UI 的主要入口点 路由组件是 URL 的集合
patterns that point to a specific component which is defined in the Pages
指向在 Pages 目录中定义的特定组件的模式
directory all pages are automatically imported here keeping your code nice and
所有页面都会自动导入这里，使您的代码保持
concise in addition all pages are automatically lazy loaded with code
简洁明了此外所有页面都会自动延迟加载代码
splitting making your load times as fast as possible it also contains a layout
拆分，使您的加载时间尽可能快它还包含一个布局
system to share UI across different routes now the back end is organized in
系统现在可以跨不同路由共享 UI，后端组织在
the API directory which uses Prisma to manage the database schema but also
使用 Prisma 管理的 API 目录中e 数据库模式，但还
provides the tools required to build a full-fledged graphql API to access your
提供构建成熟的 graphql API 以访问您的
data the back end can also Define its own custom serverless functions or
数据所需的工具，后端还可以定义自己的自定义无服务器函数或
directives which operate like middleware to handle concerns like user
指令，这些函数或指令像中间件一样运行，以处理用户身份验证等问题。
authentication what's really cool though is Redwood provides an abstraction
虽然 Redwood 真的很酷提供
called a cell to simplify complex data fetching a cell is just a component that
称为单元格的抽象来简化复杂数据获取单元格只是一个
manages a graphql query allowing you to clearly Define different states like
管理 graphql 查询的组件，允许您清楚地定义不同的状态，如
loading error and success like angular or rails Redwood provides strong
加载错误和成功，如角度或轨道 Redwood 提供强大的
conventions and a CLI to generate the boilerplate code for you use it to
约定和 CLI 来生成样板代码 因为你用它来
quickly create a component page or cell along with the code for jest and
快速创建一个组件页面或单元格以及
storybook for testing and finally use the CLI to deploy the app to your
用于测试的笑话和故事书的代码，最后使用 CLI 将应用程序部署到你
favorite serverless Cloud platform this has been Redwood JS in 100 seconds hit
最喜欢的无服务器云平台这已经是 Redwood JS 在 100 秒内
the like button and subscribe if you want to see more short videos like this
点击喜欢按钮和 如果您想看更多这样的短视频，请订阅
thanks for watching and I will see you in the next one
感谢收看，我们会在 下一个